{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259835152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259835152"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259841945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259841945"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259848063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259848062"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259857381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259857381"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 177dd079-04d9-418e-9907-71de053a8447"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Panya wana meno ya mbele makubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259869711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259869711"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259870021","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259870020"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259870623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259870623"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259873638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259873638"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259876516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259876516"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259877155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259877154"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259877922","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259877922"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259880985","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259880985"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259882557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259882557"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259883150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259883150"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259883827","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259883826"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259884683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259884683"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259885606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259885605"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259885723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259885723"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259886243","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259886243"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259888949","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259888948"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259889879","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259889878"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259890289","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259890289"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259890398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259890397"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259891536","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259891536"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259891779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259891779"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259892288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259892288"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259892542","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259892541"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259893424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259893424"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259893926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259893926"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259896763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259896763"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259897664","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259897664"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259898153","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259898153"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259898261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259898260"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259899286","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259899285"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259899544","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259899544"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259900222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259900222"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259901060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259901060"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259904164","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259904164"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259904466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259904465"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259905218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259905217"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259905517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259905516"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259905609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259905609"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259906710","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259906709"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259906976","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259906976"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259907615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259907615"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259908673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259908673"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259908847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259908846"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259909628","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259909627"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259910120","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259910119"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259913148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259913148"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259913703","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259913702"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259913767","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259913767"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259914640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259914640"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259915060","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259915060"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259915147","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259915147"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259916138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259916138"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259916340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259916339"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259917042","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259917041"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259917554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259917554"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259917747","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259917747"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259918532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259918532"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259921539","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259921539"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259921636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259921636"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259922655","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259922655"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259924283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259924283"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259925607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259925607"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259926059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259926058"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259926516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259926516"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259927680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259927679"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259928368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259928366"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259928942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259928942"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259931549","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259931548"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259932236","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259932235"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259933350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259933350"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUPENDA"," userResponse":" HUPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259934031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259934031"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259935410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259935410"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu hupenda watu kufurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHI"," userResponse":" KUFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259938133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259938133"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPENDI"," userResponse":" HAPENDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259938935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259938935"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGOMVI"," userResponse":" UGOMVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259939688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259939688"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALA"," userResponse":" WALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259940187","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259940187"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapendi ugomvi wala vita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITA"," userResponse":" VITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259943550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259943550"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWAALIKA"," userResponse":" HUWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259944563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259944563"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259945645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259945644"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANGALIA"," userResponse":" KUANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259946422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259946422"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259947095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259947094"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259947512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259947511"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKA"," userResponse":" DUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259948056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259948055"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259951647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259951647"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWATEMBELEA"," userResponse":" HUWATEMBELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259952661","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259952660"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAGONJWA"," userResponse":" WAGONJWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259953201","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259953200"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259953929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259953929"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZEE"," userResponse":" WAZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259954809","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259954809"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259955270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259955269"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259955818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259955818"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwatembelea wagonjwa na wazee katika nyumba zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259958893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259958892"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259960180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259960180"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" APITAPO"," userResponse":" APITAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259961135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259961135"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259961900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259961900"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259962232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259962232"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259962837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259962836"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259963816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259963815"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259965956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259965956"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259966848","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259966848"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bi Simu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259969585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259969584"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259970692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259970689"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" HUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259970890","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259970890"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259971559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259971558"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259973142","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259973141"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259973995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259973995"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259974186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259974186"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259974716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259974716"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259975308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259975308"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259975754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259975753"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259976228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259976228"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259976997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259976996"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259978355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259978355"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye hufurahia na kusema Mimi ni Bi Simu na hizi simu zangu ziangalieni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIANGALIENI"," userResponse":" ZIANGALIENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259980603","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259980603"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259980782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259980782"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259980942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259980942"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259981565","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259981564"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259982024","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259982024"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259982545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259982545"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259983031","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259983031"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259983563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259983562"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259986379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259986376"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259986516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259986516"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548259993113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548259993112"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" f6f132c9-6754-4075-ad20-260dd987578d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huyo ni Bi Simu na simu zake tano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260003137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260003137"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 6ab36f72-2719-4046-a364-a86617767b47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-0-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260005557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260005556"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 6ab36f72-2719-4046-a364-a86617767b47"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-0-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260016339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260016339"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-u-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260020884","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260020884"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260025222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260025221"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_u-i-e"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260029285","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260029285"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260033926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260033926"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260039665","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260039664"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260052288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260052288"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 12c4a162-d255-436e-b80d-0c73eaa38170"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.26"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-o-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260065843","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260065843"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-O-T"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260070874","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260070874"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_I-W-O"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260075816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260075816"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_J-A-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260080444","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260080444"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_P-F-L"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260086016","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260086016"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_G-N-CH"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260090557","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260090556"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_E-T-Y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260095150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260095150"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_S-P-M"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260099735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260099735"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-Z-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260104877","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260104877"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_H-B-Y"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260109761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260109761"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-T-K"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260115059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260115058"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_M-CH-L"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260119438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260119438"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_J-K-Y"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260124073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260124072"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_S-D-W"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260128196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260128196"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_O-G-S"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260132581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260132581"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260137012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260137012"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_B-R-T"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260144086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260144086"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_N-D-I"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260150750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260150750"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_G-N-Y"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260155686","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260155686"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_J-A-R"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260159919","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260159919"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_M-I-CH"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260164504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260164504"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260170375","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260170375"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-K-F"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260176188","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260176188"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-D-Z"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260179684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260179684"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_B-A-L"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260184234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260184234"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260189991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260189989"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 18e7ec4d-2ceb-4c33-89a2-6e3b8068aba4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.77"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_E_E-Y-R"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260202402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260202402"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260209861","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260209861"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-9-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260216012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260216012"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_7-1-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260221821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260221821"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_0-5-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260226563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260226563"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260230677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260230676"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 3b3b1c58-a65f-412c-b7ec-a4691b1aeb87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.x2s.Ax.rise.42__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260241419","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260241419"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 52bc40fa-dd1c-47c0-8a01-5152cfba935c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260242337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260242337"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 52bc40fa-dd1c-47c0-8a01-5152cfba935c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260251862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260251862"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 52bc40fa-dd1c-47c0-8a01-5152cfba935c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260285515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260285514"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" 52bc40fa-dd1c-47c0-8a01-5152cfba935c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260285586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260285586"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c371b2a7-d481-42fb-91ac-dd562a9dc0e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260295998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260295998"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-k-z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260301974","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260301974"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-k-z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260305283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260305282"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-z-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260310008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260310007"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-a-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260315073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260315073"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_g-a-d"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260319988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260319988"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-o-y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260323725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260323725"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_n-a-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260328849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260328849"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-v-k"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260334756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260334756"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-v-k"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260337969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260337969"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_w-y-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260341527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260341527"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_y-m-i"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260345184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260345184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_s-m-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260349377","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260349377"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-l"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260352857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260352857"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-p-v"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260355925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260355925"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-y-w"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260359593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260359592"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_j-l-p"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260363204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260363204"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-i-ch"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260366246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260366245"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-v-e"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260369568","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260369568"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_g-j-z"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260372969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260372969"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-n-k"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260376337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260376337"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-m-f"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260380194","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260380194"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_h-r-e"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260384618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260384618"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_o-b-l"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260389671","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260389671"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_l-k-j"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260393168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260393168"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-y-h"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260398091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260398091"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_t-i-n"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260405085","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260405084"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260410862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260410858"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548260455613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548260455613"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_191020"," gameId":" c1747168-a804-4971-ade2-49786f89e6f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_h_v-h-l"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}